(Sheldon:)Oh. By the way, I was watching you sleep
for a moment.
I noticed your snoring seems to be worse
when you're on your back.
No. Leonard doesn't snore.
(Sheldon:)No. I wasn't talking to Leonard.
(Leonard:)Told you.
(Employment Office Assistant:)So, Mr. Cooper,
you're looking for a job.
(Sheldon:)A menial job.
(Sheldon:)Like yours.
(Assistant:)Why, thank you for noticing.
(Assistant:)I'm menial employee of the month.
(Assistant:)Do you have a particular field in mind?
(Sheldon:)I do. For thousands of years...
(Sheldon:)...the lowest classes of the human race
have spent their lives laboring...
(Sheldon:)...to erect monuments
under the lash of betters.
(Sheldon:)Until finally they dropped down
and became one with the dust...
(Sheldon:)...through which they trudged.
(Sheldon:)Do you have anything like that?
(Penny:)-No.
-Shouldn't you check your database?